

My name is I was born on the 11th of September in 2002. I was born and raised in Leiden, the Netherlands. After I completed high school in 2021 and got my VWO-diploma, I decided that I wanted to go to Spain to learn Spanish. This was an amazing experience and I managed to learn it quite well. After coming back to the Netherlands I decided I wanted to go back and follow my dreams. I've been to Madrid last year in March and immediately fell in love with the city. I think this job would fit me very well, as it seems like a great adventure to me and I like to do new things. I'm a hard worker, and a fast learner.

Education:

VWO-diploma, obtained at Winford High School in Leiden in 2021.

Job experience:

- Barman/waiter at Taberna de Jarana in Malaga, Spain. *Sep. 2022-May. 2023;*
- Meal deliverer and manager at Maciotto in Leiden, the Netherlands. *Apr.* 2019-Aug. 2022;
- Stock clerk at Albert Heijn Supermarket in Leiden, the Netherlands. Sep. 2017-Dec.2018.

Working these jobs I've learned how to handle money, how to work hard and above all, how to satisfy customers and keep them happy. I've gotten in contact with lots of different people of lots of different backgrounds and cultures.

Languages:

- Dutch: Native language, C2;

English: C2;Spanish: C1German: A2

In my daily life I mainly use English and Dutch. In Malaga I've spoken Spanish both at the language school to learn words and grammar, and later while working in a bar amongst the locals. The German I know is from my time at high school.